I need you.
I hope you'll keep
lending me your strength.
Dice Thrust!
Critical.
Golden Raana are worth a lot of EXP,
but the best part is
the valuable item drops.
The drop rate is 50%.
Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade.
Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade
Attack: +12.
Market price: 17,000,000 gold.
Attack: +12
Market Price: 17,000,000G
A glittering Raana short sword
A hunk of high-purity Raana Gold
A glittering Raana short sword.
A hunk of high-purity Raana Gold.
We got a Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade!
Loading
Begin Adventure
Episode 8
Wandering
W-Wow, we acquired
a 1,700,000 gold item so easily.
Hold on. You're missing a digit.
You're one zero short.
What?
It's worth 17,000,000 gold.
Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade
Attack: +12
Market Price: 17,000,000G
One, ten, hundred, thousand,
ten thousand, hundred thousand, million...
My party kicked me over
my share of a 2,000,000 gold item.
Have you calmed down a little?
Yes, somewhat.
But I still can't believe we acquired
such a valuable item so easily.
Maybe that's odd for me to say
after you set this up, but still...
Carrying this rare item around
will make us a target!
Mr. Elymas, let's run away together!
We can hide away in some remote place!
Yes, that's what we should do. Yup, yup.
Well... you're not wrong.
We should get going.
We'll farm one more before the sun sets.
What? Another one?
3 Hours Later
Three hours later.
Dice Thrust!
Miss.
Again!
Dice Thrust!
Miss.
I'll get it this time! Dice Thrust!
Critical.
We did it, Ruche. That's our second one.
Level 33 reached.
Ruche?
You missed a few times, but just imagine
you're saving your luck for later.
Thirty...
Thirty-four million...
Ruche?
Pull yourself together, Ruche!
Th-Thirty million...
Ten times 3,000,000?
Thanks to you, we got two
Dazzling Raana Decorative Blades.
We'll have to consider how best
to use this money for our party.
Y-You're right. We need to think
about our future.
But it still doesn't feel real.
We'll need to consider how to spend
our skill points given our equipment.
Oh, right. I still have skill points
from gaining all those levels.
How should I spend them?
You really shouldn't be
showing that to people.
There's no need to worry
about that anymore.
I owe you for getting me to this level.
I wouldn't mind if you used me up
and threw me away like a rag.
I really wish you did.
What is it?
A voice?
What voice?
Did you hear a crying baby just now?
A crying baby?
Could it be?
It's wandering.
Wandering
A dungeon's boss
or Dreamlord is its heart.
Dreamlord
Normally, it stays put
deep inside the dungeon.
But sometimes it wanders around
the rest of the dungeon.
Wandering
That's known as wandering.
Wandering?
Isn't this Dreamlord's
recommended level 50?
Isn't that bad news?
We're fine. If we take the right steps,
we can avoid it.
We'll move away from
the voice and towards the exit.
The Dreamlord won't follow us outside.
Really? That's a relief.
Yeah. It's that simple.
We'll head to the exit
and cash out back in town.
That's where this adventure should end.
But
But...
Help!
I was naive.
A much stronger monster suddenly appeared!
Are you okay? Hang in there!
This isn't a game.
What happened?
They'll never escape like that.
Deep in the dungeon...
If we flee now,
these two will definitely die.
Ruche, take them outside!
I'll keep the monster occupied!
Okay, but not even you
can handle a level 50 Dreamlord!
I know its nature.
I can buy time for you
and escape by myself.
Besides...
it's a Heavy Knight's job
to draw aggro.
Mr. Elymas...
There you are...
Tin Knight.
Help!
A much stronger monster suddenly appeared!
Are you okay?
This isn't a game.
I'll buy time for you.
Ruche, take them and go.
B-But...
Th-Thank you so much.
Monster: Tin Knight
I see. It's damaged.
The situation could be worse.
My. Elymas, it's a powerful monster,
but it's weakened.
Let's defeat it together.
No. We can't, Ruche.
You have to run.
But...
The Tin Knight isn't the Dreamlord itself.
That's just one of its minions.
The actual Dreamlord will arrive soon.
No way.
Three level 40s?
I'll be right behind you
once I've bought some time.
Y-You can't do this.
I can't leave you to
handle these by yourself.
You invited me to join your party.
Do I have to spell it out?
I can't look out for dead weight
while fighting these guys.
You'd just get in the way.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Don't take too long, Mr. Elymas.
Three level 40s, huh?
Ruche and I might've been able
to take them out if she stayed.
But...
the Dreamlord is still out there.
I told Ruche I'd draw them to me
and flee, but that was a lie.
As a Heavy Knight, I have no speed.
I might be able to escape
from Tin Knights.
But running from a Dreamlord
with magic attacks...
is impossible.
I'll defeat the Dreamlord here.
There you are, Dreamlord Embryo!
Dreamlord:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hEmbryo
The Embryo's stats are low
for a level 50 monster.
The problem is that
I can't deal damage to it.
Its flesh's Defense is unbelievably high.
Only its eye can be damaged,
and that requires ranged attacks.
But...
if it's a got a weakness, then even
a low-level solo adventurer can beat it.
Skill Trees: Heavy Knight
Remaining Skill Points: 9
Oath of the Heavy Armor
Defense Booster
Beginner Swordsmanship
Oath of the Heavy Armor
has reached level 27.
Oath of the Heavy Armor has reached level 27
Shield Bash skill has been acquired
Shield Bash skill has been acquired.
Let's go, Embryo!
Don't worry, I won't run!
I'll fight you head-on!
Shield... Bash!
Shield Bash [Common Skill]
Push an enemy with a shield and knock them back
Skill: Shield Bash.
Push an enemy with a shield
and knock them back.
I'm glad to have this skill
that lets me split up my enemies.
Parry!
Disarm!
The Embryo won't use either of its magic
attacks, Sylph Cutter and Thunderstorm,
if it would hit the Tin Knights.
I can focus on the Tin Knights.
Disarm!
Disarm
That's the second hit.
It's only been 47 seconds
since the first Disarm.
I've met the activation conditions.
Rampart Reflection
Rampart Reflection!
The real battle starts now.
That's one down.
But...
Repair
The Tin Knights will keep reviving
unless I defeat the Embryo.
But it exposes its eye when it uses magic.
Take this!
That's my only attack that reaches it.
Earth Magic Stone.
Spend MP to fire
countless needles of earth.
Earth Magic Stone Patchwork Bear
Spend MP to fire countless needles of earth
I'll use the Tin Knight
to block its Sylph Cutter.
As long as I don't screw this up,
I won't be one-shot.
Shield Bash!
What?!
Vital Slice!
They're learning.
In Magic World, monsters
couldn't adapt to player skills.
They've clearly learned
what Shield Bash looks like.
This isn't unexpected.
But this makes beating
the Embryo way harder.
I need to throw three more
Magic Stones to beat it,
and Dreamlords regenerate quickly.
If I take too long, I'm screwed.
No way. It shouldn't use Sylph Cutter
with this positioning.
Sylph Cutter
It's no use.
I can't avoid it.
My consciousness is fading.
My heart is racing.
My legs feel weak.
Status Effect
Stunned
Status effect: Stunned.
I see. Well, a stun is fatal
in this situation.
Maybe my starting Luck value was low.
I should've asked Ruche to stay.
Let's defeat it together.
You called?
Thanks for choosing me.
Translator:
Sho Stifler
Timer:
Krzysztof Kunc
Editor:
Salem Alabanza
Quality Control:
Gabriella Alabanza
Final Quality Control:
Sriram Gurunathan
I wasn't overconfident.
I fought the best I could've.
But I couldn't quite beat
the Embryo Dreamlord.
It was Ruche who saved me.
She put herself in danger
by coming to rescue me.
So I—we'll defeat the Embryo together.
We'll beat this dungeon.
Next time, "Dreamlord."
Far more than I imagined, Ruche is...